LAURA MARSH

1630 Stanford, Irvine, CA 92612 Cell: 510.456.8670 - la.ly.marsh@gmail.com

OBIECTIVE

I am pursuing a BS degree and currently targeting an internship opportunity in the field of Computer Science and Software Engineering across multiple platforms. I'm intrigued by the process behind a project's conception to its creation and delivery. I have experience in object-oriented programming; debugging, testing, and developing code; and designing interfaces.

I'm a team player and a quick and passionate learner, with a drive to learn from the best and succeed in my field.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering University of California, Irvine

October 2014 - June 2018, current

- Member of the School of Information and Computer Science Student Council
- Affiliated with Theta Tau, a coed engineering fraternity
- Coursework in Web Design and Development, Data Structures, Software Design and Processes, Object-**Oriented Programming**

SKILLS & ABILITIES ____

- Proficient in Python, Java, C++
- Experience with Vim
- Proficient with Windows, Linux, Unix
- Experience with Git
- Experience with MS Visual Studio, Eclipse, Android Studio

- Experience with XML/HTML/Javascript
- Advanced problem solving
- Troubleshooting and debugging
- Exceptional time management
- **Experience using Ubuntu**

EXPERIENCE ____

December 2016 - current Android OS Developer

Inwerks - Rancho Santa Margarita, CA

- Used Ubuntu and Android Studio to develop the Android OS version of the Inwerks application.
- Modified existing software to correct previous errors, upgrade the user interface, and improve overall look and performance.

June 2015 – October 2015 Firmware Intern

Dell EMC - DSSD - Menlo Park, CA

- Used Python, git, linux to build and run product tests.
- Modified existing software to correct errors, adapt to new hardware and improve performance.
- Drafted reports to document bugs and design flaws.
- Performed regression and system-level testing to verify quality and function.

June 2015 – October 2015 Home Appraisal Assistant

Akimi Appraisal – Fremont, CA

Filed reports and evaluations, negotiated service fees, and scheduled and maintained appointments.